DONGHYEON SHIN

(+82) 10 7736 8525 ♦ shindong97411@gmail.com 123, Cheomdangwagi-ro, Buk-gu, Gwangju Republic of Korea, 61005

Personal Statement

Passionate graduate student studying artificial intelligence. Interested in Natural Language Processing and Reinforcement Learning. I am focusing on research towards Artificial General Intelligence, with a primary emphasis on the most prominent Large Language Models and Skill-based Reinforcement Learning.

EDUCATION

Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology(GIST)

Undergraduate

Major in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

Minor in Mathematics

UC Berkeley

Berkeley Summer Session Program

Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology(GIST)

March 2018 - February 2024

Overall GPA: 3.71/4.50

June 2019 - August 2019

Overall GPA: 4.00/4.00

March 2018 - Ongoing

Overall GPA: 4.08/4.50

Major in Artificial Intelligence

ACADEMIC ACTIVITIES

Publications

- · Seungpil Lee*, Woochang Sim*, **Donghyeon Shin***, Sanha Hwang, Wongyu Seo, Jiwon Park, Seokki Lee, Sejin Kim, and Sundong Kim, Reasoning Abilities of Large Language Models: In-Depth Analysis on the Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus, **ACM TIST** (2024)
- · Donghyeon Shin*, Seungpil Lee*, Klea Lena Kovačec, and Sundong Kim, From Generation to Selection: Findings of converting Analogical Problem-Solving into Multiple-Choice Questions, EMNLP Findings (2024)
- · Donghyeon Shin, Seungpil Lee, Klea Lena Kovačec, and Sundong Kim, Regulation Using Large Language Models to Generate Synthetic Data for Evaluating Analogical Ability, IJCAI Workshop (2024)
- · Donghyeon Shin, Sanha Hwang, Seokki Lee, Yunho Kim, Seungpil Lee, and Sundong Kim, MC-LARC Benchmark to Measure LLM Reasoning Capability, Korea Software Congress (2023)
- · Jaehyun Park, Jagyun Im, Youngdo Lee, **Donghyeon Shin**, Sejin Kim, and Sundong Kim, Abstraction and Reasoning Challenge with Decision Transformer, Korea Computer Congress (2023)
- · Jinseong Son, **Donghyeon Shin**, and Chi-Ok Hwang, Walk-on-Hemispheres First-Passage Algorithm, Scientific Reports (2023)

SKILLS

Computer Languages C, C++, Python
Software & Tools & Framework
Language Language, English(Intermediate)

FUNDING & SCHOLARSHIP

Korean Government Scholarships, GIST College

March 2024 - Present

· Scholarship awarded to graduate students studying in GIST

National Research Foundation of Korea Funding, NRF

July 2024 - Present

· Funding offered to eligible master's students for conducting research projects

Korean Government Scholarships, GIST College

March 2018 - February 2024

· Scholarship awarded to undergraduate students studying in GIST

Scholarship for Summer Session Abroad

June 2019 - August 2019

· Scholarship awarded to students studying abroad during a summer session

EXPERIENCE

DataScience Lab in GIST

March 2024 - Present

Master Student

- · Proposed a new benchmark called Multi-Choice Language ARC (MC-LARC)
- · Researched the reasoning ability of LLMs

DataScience Lab in GIST

March 2023 - February 2024

Undergraduate Internship

· Tried to solve Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) benchmark using Skill-based Reinforcement Learning